[
  {
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "How old your elder brother was 10 years before you was born, mate?",
        "correct_answer": 1,
        "answers": [
          "11 years",
          "10 years",
          "14 years",
          "12 years"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "How old your elder brother was 14 years before you was born, mate?",
        "correct_answer": 3,
        "answers": [
          "10 years",
          "11 years",
          "12 years",
          "14 years"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "How old your elder brother was 11 years before you was born, mate?",
        "correct_answer": 0,
        "answers": [
          "11 years",
          "14 years",
          "12 years",
          "10 years"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "How old your elder brother was 11 years before you was born, mate?",
        "correct_answer": 0,
        "answers": [
          "11 years",
          "14 years",
          "12 years",
          "10 years"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "How old your elder brother was 11 years before you was born, mate?",
        "correct_answer": 0,
        "answers": [
          "11 years",
          "14 years",
          "12 years",
          "10 years"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "How old your elder brother was 11 years before you was born, mate?",
        "correct_answer": 0,
        "answers": [
          "11 years",
          "14 years",
          "12 years",
          "10 years"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "How old your elder brother was 11 years before you was born, mate?",
        "correct_answer": 0,
        "answers": [
          "11 years",
          "14 years",
          "12 years",
          "10 years"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "How old your elder brother was 11 years before you was born, mate?",
        "correct_answer": 0,
        "answers": [
          "11 years",
          "14 years",
          "12 years",
          "10 years"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "How old your elder brother was 11 years before you was born, mate?",
        "correct_answer": 0,
        "answers": [
          "11 years",
          "14 years",
          "12 years",
          "10 years"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "How old your elder brother was 11 years before you was born, mate?",
        "correct_answer": 0,
        "answers": [
          "11 years",
          "14 years",
          "12 years",
          "10 years"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "How old your elder brother was 11 years before you was born, mate?",
        "correct_answer": 0,
        "answers": [
          "11 years",
          "14 years",
          "12 years",
          "10 years"
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "step_array": [
      500,
      1000,
      2000,
      4000,
      8000,
      16000,
      32000,
      64000,
      125000,
      250000,
      500000,
      1000000
    ]
  }
]
